bibleinfo.com 2018-10-17

# Privacy Policy | Bibleinfo.com

## You are here

Your privacy is important to Bibleinfo.com. As a user of our website, you will learn about the Bible perhaps for yourself, perhaps on behalf of someone else. At Bibleinfo.com, we understand that your spiritual life is a personal and private subject, and we want you to feel as comfortable as possible visiting our website and using its services. This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect, how we protect it and what choices you have about how that information is used. We urge you to read our Privacy Policy so that you will understand both our commitment to you and your privacy, and how you can participate in that commitment.

The following Articles make up our Privacy Policy. We hope that reading them gives you a clear idea of how we manage information regarding you. For immediate access to a particular topic, click on the title of that Article.

  * ARTICLE 1: Personal Information We Collect
  * ARTICLE 2: Disclosure of Your Information
  * ARTICLE 3: How Bibleinfo.com Handles Privacy Internally
  * ARTICLE 4: Your Privacy Choices
  * ARTICLE 5: Updating Your Personal Information and Contacting Bibleinfo.com
  * ARTICLE 6: Acceptance of Privacy and Security Policy

Please remember that any information that you reveal in a public forum (such as a bulletin board, mail list, chat room/event) is not subject to this Privacy Policy and will be seen by third parties not related to Bibleinfo.com and may be used by them to contact you for unauthorized purposes. Also, if you link to a third party site from Bibleinfo.com, any information you reveal on that site is not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should consult the privacy policies of each site you visit.

ARTICLE 1

###  Personal Information We Collect  

  1. We collect information in several distinct areas: When you browse to our site and when you Ask a Bible Question, submit a Prayer Request, and request our Free Gift. The information we collect in these areas is as follows: 
    1. IP Address 
    2. Ask a Bible Question and Prayer Request, and Contact Us sections 
    3. First name* 
    4. Email address* 
    5. For the Gift Request Section 
    6. Full Name* 
    7. Address* 
    8. City, State/Prov, Postal Code* 
    9. Country* 
    10. Email address* 
  2. Bibleinfo.com only uses browser cookies to store information about settings language related on this site, so that when you return to Bibleinfo.com, you will see your desired language. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the site or our products and services, and you can choose to refuse our cookie, delete our cookie from your hard drive or turn off the cookie at any time by updating 
  3. At times, Bibleinfo.com uses the user's IP address to derive the approximate City, State/Province, and Country of the user. 

*Required information. Provision of any other information is optional.  
 All web servers collect the client's IP address. This is required in order to provide the client with the requested web pages.

ARTICLE 2

###  Disclosure of Your Information  

Except as set forth in this paragraph, Bibleinfo.com will not disclose to anyone any information it gathers from you which could be used to identify or contact you ("Personal Information"). Any Personal Information provided to entities affiliated with Bibleinfo.com will be treated in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, unless you are otherwise notified.

In the following limited circumstances we will consider, and may release, Personal Information to third parties: (1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; (2) to follow-up on special requests initiated by you, such as delivery of the materials requested by you; (3) to notify you of other related resources and services in your area; (4) in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others.

Bibleinfo.com may provide some information to third parties about you which does not allow you to be identified or contacted ("Aggregate Information"). For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of our site and the activities they conduct while on our site. We might also inform a company that "30% of our users live east of the Mississippi" or that "25% of our users have made a prayer request."

ARTICLE 3

###  How Bibleinfo.com Handles Privacy Internally  

Bibleinfo.com wants your personal information to remain as secure as reasonably possible. That is why we have a two-tier system at Bibleinfo.com that combines leading technical safeguards and a code of conduct for those employees that are permitted to access our customers' personal information. On the technical side, Bibleinfo.com uses all means available to help ensure the integrity and privacy of the Personal Information you provide to us via the Internet. As an additional security measure, your Personal Information is also kept physically separate on a separate server. On the employee side, only authorized Bibleinfo.com employees are permitted to access your personal information. All Bibleinfo.com employees must abide by our Privacy Policy and those who violate our Privacy Policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

ARTICLE 4

###  Your Privacy Choices  

You may opt out of submitting your Personal Information at the time you provide the information necessary to facilitate your request.

ARTICLE 5

###  Updating Your Personal Information and Contacting Bibleinfo.com  

We will always strive to make the changing of your personal options as easy as possible.

You can always contact us in order to (i) delete your Personal Information from our systems, (ii) update the Personal Information that you have provided to us, by contact us.

Bibleinfo.com may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our website. Your use of the site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately.

ARTICLE 6

###  Acceptance of Privacy and Security Policy  

By using this site and services, you signify your acceptance of our privacy and security policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy and Security Notice, your only remedy is to discontinue use of this site and services. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy and Security Notice at any time. If we change our policy, we will post those changes on our site so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of any portion of the site following notification or posting of such changes will constitute your acceptance of those changes. Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you.
